<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss version='2.0' xmlns:itunes='http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd'>
<channel>
<title>The Emperor's Court : An Original Media For Gamers Production</title>
<link>http://www.omfg.fm</link>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>2011 Original Media for Gamers</copyright>
<itunes:subtitle>The Emperor's Court</itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:author>Emperor</itunes:author>
<itunes:summary>The Emperor's Court</itunes:summary>
<description>Since 2001, the Emperor's Court and its prior incarnations have been gracing the Internet with its presence. Tackling online gaming news, game reviews, and the general stupidity that is life on the Internet help to fill this 2 hour show with comedy, serious business and absolute horror. Featuring popular segments The Quickening, Stupid Moments in Gaming History and well written, original skits. Hosted by award winning broadcaster Emperor[1G] and Highlander[1G], the Emperor's Court is your two hour break from Internet porn.</description>
<itunes:owner>
<itunes:name>Emperor</itunes:name>
<itunes:email>emperor1g@cox.net</itunes:email>
</itunes:owner>
<itunes:image href='http://www.omfg.fm/images/shows/ec-235x150.png'/>
<image>
<link>http://www.omfg.fm</link>
<url>http://www.omfg.fm/images/shows/ec-235x150.png</url>
<title>The Emperor's Court : An Original Media For Gamers Production</title>
<width>144</width>
<height>150</height>
</image>
<itunes:category text='Games &amp; Hobbies'>
<itunes:category text='Video Games'/>
</itunes:category>
<itunes:category text='Technology'>
<itunes:category text='Podcasting'/>
</itunes:category>
<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
<item>
<title>The Emperor's Court - Eps. 16 New Equipment!</title>
<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Eps. 16 New Equipment!</itunes:summary>
<description>On this episode of the Emperor's Court, the new Verse the World Productions network debuts, as we now stream to our newest affiliate!

We also debut the pimp new equipment that was purchased with the donations from our most generous listeners. Now the sound quality is that of a couple of professionals even as we cast like a couple of noobs!

Topics covered:

13 year old girl flogged 90 times in Saudi Arabia for having a cell phone

Highlander mommy gives him a new phone

"This or That" segment goes over some of the finer video games of yesteryear,  Sonic vs. Mario Brothers, Street Fighter vs. Mortal Kombat, including a spirited debate of Ultima Online vs. World of Warcraft

Jediism is a real religion? Really? Really.

"Meltdown": Environmentalist freaks want people to be rewarded in World of Warcraft for being "green" IRL.

"Stupid Video Game Moment of the Week": Final Fantasy IX's failure of a strategy guide that prevented its buyers from actually using it</description>
<itunes:duration>02:21:07</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Emperor,Court</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
<pubDate>Jan 26, 2010 02:13 AM</pubDate>
<enclosure type='audio/mpeg' url='http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec012210.mp3' length='1'/>
<link>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec012210.mp3</link>
<guid>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec012210.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Emperor's Court - Eps. 15 Future of the show announced!</title>
<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Eps. 15 Future of the show announced!</itunes:summary>
<description>In this exciting episode, Emperor and Highlander reveal the future of the Emperor's Court. It rather more hysterical episode (I know, hard to do right?) then even the normal nuttiness, but our topics include:

Google's hypocrisy in China

Sooooo many games coming out this Spring

Review of games gained over Christmas

Meltdown: Vegans complain about lack of recipes in World of Warcraft

Either/Or: Highlander answers the tough questions Emperor puts to him

Stupidest Video Game Moment: Nintendo punished for their monopolistic ways by being forced to sell MORE games...


</description>
<itunes:duration>02:04:52</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Emperor,Court</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
<pubDate>Jan 26, 2010 02:11 AM</pubDate>
<enclosure type='audio/mpeg' url='http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec011510.mp3' length='1'/>
<link>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec011510.mp3</link>
<guid>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec011510.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Emperor's Court - Episode 14 Questions answered, Emp solo, future?</title>
<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Episode 14 Questions answered, Emp solo, future?</itunes:summary>
<description>In this episode, Emperor flies solo as Highlander is snowed in. The questions as to why WCRadio is closing its doors are answered, and the future of Emperor's Court is explained.

A definitive answer will come on the January 16th show.

topics:

Video games are 4th on the list of things that entertain kids these days. Kids are fat.

Electronic Arts stands behind Tiger Woods for an online golf game.

MAG gets ready to debut later this month, what does this massive game hold for us, the player? Will it reach its potential?

Stupid Video Game Moment of the week: Several stories are read of various players around the world of offed themselves or did something else stupid as it relates to gaming.

Meltdown: Greenpeace attacks Nintendo and Microsoft on their e-waste and enviro-friendly business practices.</description>
<itunes:duration>01:56:24</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Emperor,Court</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
<pubDate>Jan 26, 2010 02:10 AM</pubDate>
<enclosure type='audio/mpeg' url='http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec010910.mp3' length='1'/>
<link>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec010910.mp3</link>
<guid>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec010910.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Emperor's Court - Episode 13 Emp poisons Santa (irl) and Highlander sings!</title>
<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Episode 13 Emp poisons Santa (irl) and Highlander sings!</itunes:summary>
<description>Emperor and Highlander break down the results of Spike TV's Video Game Awards with surprising accuracy. There is talk of $5000 gold played Playstation 3's and other Mac related hardware, plus discussion of the advancement in Nerf weaponry over the years  (Emp bought a fully automatic, ammo belt fed, tripod mounted Nerf machine gun). Emp and Highlander swap Christmas stories, and Highlander sings for the Quickening!</description>
<itunes:duration>02:04:05</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Emperor,Court</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
<pubDate>Jan 26, 2010 02:09 AM</pubDate>
<enclosure type='audio/mpeg' url='http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec121809.mp3' length='1'/>
<link>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec121809.mp3</link>
<guid>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec121809.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Emperor's Court - Episode 12 VGA predictions, She-Ra, war?</title>
<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Episode 12 VGA predictions, She-Ra, war?</itunes:summary>
<description>In this episode, Emperor and Highlander switch places on their tried and true trademark segments. Emperor does the Quickening and Highlander does the Meltdown. The VGA awards are discussed in detail, with Emperor and Highlander making their predictions on what SpikeTV will choose to win various categories, but also what THEY would choose were they the judges.

Articles discussed in regards to Brazil's government putting forth a bill to block "offensive" video games, some breaking news that interrupted the show, and a reminder to listeners who She-Ra is.</description>
<itunes:duration>02:18:56</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Emperor,Court</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
<pubDate>Jan 26, 2010 02:07 AM</pubDate>
<enclosure type='audio/mpeg' url='http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec121109.mp3' length='1'/>
<link>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec121109.mp3</link>
<guid>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec121109.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Emperor's Court - Eps. 11 Online clans = IRL gangs? Seriously.</title>
<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Eps. 11 Online clans = IRL gangs? Seriously.</itunes:summary>
<description>On this episode, sanity and normalcy returns to the Emperor's Court as Emperor regains control of the board.  Debate over the study that online guilds and clans are the same as in real life street gangs. The Spike TV Video Game Awards are coming up and our thoughts on them. Kexman and Almighty-Farseer from Essence of Role-Playing air a horrid impression of Emperor on their show, prompting delcarations of retaliation.

And next week, Emperor will take over the Quickening!</description>
<itunes:duration>02:14:06</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Emperor,Court</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
<pubDate>Jan 26, 2010 02:05 AM</pubDate>
<enclosure type='audio/mpeg' url='http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec120409.mp3' length='1'/>
<link>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec120409.mp3</link>
<guid>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec120409.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Emperor's Court - Eps. 10 Highlander takes over the Court!</title>
<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Eps. 10 Highlander takes over the Court!</itunes:summary>
<description>Highlander runs the board tonight, taking over all aspects of the show with his own personal touch. Heavy debates about individual digital rights, Emperor meltsdown on the Xbox/Wal-mart conspiracy, and a ton more.</description>
<itunes:duration>02:00:10</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Emperor,Court</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
<pubDate>Jan 26, 2010 02:04 AM</pubDate>
<enclosure type='audio/mpeg' url='http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec112609.mp3' length='1'/>
<link>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec112609.mp3</link>
<guid>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec112609.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Emperor's Court - Emp Court Twilight Skit</title>
<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Emp Court Twilight Skit</itunes:summary>
<description>This is the uber-popular Twilight New Moon skit by Emperor and Highlander.  "To Catch a Predator" on PMSNBC hosted by  "Clark Hanson" interviews Robert Pattinson as to why he is hitting on 17 year old high school girls.</description>
<itunes:duration>00:06:21</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Emperor,Court</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
<pubDate>Jan 26, 2010 02:02 AM</pubDate>
<enclosure type='audio/mpeg' url='http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ectwilightskit.mp3' length='1'/>
<link>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ectwilightskit.mp3</link>
<guid>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ectwilightskit.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Emperor's Court - Eps. 9 Twilight sucks, MW2 doesnt, controversy!</title>
<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Eps. 9 Twilight sucks, MW2 doesnt, controversy!</itunes:summary>
<description>In this latest installment, Emperor and Highlander explore the recent controversy surrounding Modern Warfare 2, rag on countries from around the world, air a skit on Twilight meets To Catch a Predator, discuss the Top 10 Most Racist Toys, debate taking $60 in new movies vs. $60 for 1 new game.

Also, listener emails, the Quickening, and Emperor's Meltdown.</description>
<itunes:duration>02:04:28</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Emperor,Court</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
<pubDate>Jan 26, 2010 02:01 AM</pubDate>
<enclosure type='audio/mpeg' url='http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec112009.mp3' length='1'/>
<link>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec112009.mp3</link>
<guid>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec112009.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Emperor's Court - Episode 8 The Quickening Debuts</title>
<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Episode 8 The Quickening Debuts</itunes:summary>
<description>In this latest episode of the Court, Emperor and Highlander discuss emails from listeners regarding  PC gaming vs. Console gaming, digital downloading of games as opposed to purchasing hardcopy, the Quickening debuts where Highlander answers the listener questions...on any topic....with controversial and comic results.

Other side topics include Highlander's convention chairman stories, Redneck Rockband, Mafia Wars on Facebook, Gay Friendly Guilds in World of Warcraft, and more!</description>
<itunes:duration>01:56:06</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Emperor,Court</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
<pubDate>Jan 26, 2010 02:00 AM</pubDate>
<enclosure type='audio/mpeg' url='http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec111309.mp3' length='1'/>
<link>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec111309.mp3</link>
<guid>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec111309.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Emperor's Court - Episode 7 Return to LIVE!</title>
<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Episode 7 Return to LIVE!</itunes:summary>
<description>The Emperor's Court is back to airing live here on World of Warcraft Radio on Fridays 7-9pm eastern!

In this show, Emperor and Highlander discuss the Wii as a health tool according to the UK government, Facebook games are the scourge of the Internet, Console gaming vs. PC gaming cost/versatility, Highlander introduces the Quickening segment, and the Emperor's Rant focuses on Blizzard's selling of vanity pets and the release of DJ Hero.

You'll love this one</description>
<itunes:duration>01:49:08</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Emperor,Court</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
<pubDate>Jan 26, 2010 01:57 AM</pubDate>
<enclosure type='audio/mpeg' url='http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec110609.mp3' length='1'/>
<link>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec110609.mp3</link>
<guid>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec110609.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Emperor's Court - Episode 6 Follow up's and limericks!</title>
<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Episode 6 Follow up's and limericks!</itunes:summary>
<description>This week we are without the presence of Highlander[1G]. We delve into follow ups to the dying of the gaming industry, and the acquisition of Marvel by Disney. The Emperor's Rant about Jack Thompson's lawsuit against Facebook, and some emails from the listeners, with a limerick from Mystic Mimm that she isn't aware I read over the air...yet...</description>
<itunes:duration>00:48:04</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Emperor,Court</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
<pubDate>Jan 26, 2010 01:55 AM</pubDate>
<enclosure type='audio/mpeg' url='http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec100609.mp3' length='1'/>
<link>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec100609.mp3</link>
<guid>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec100609.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Emperor's Court - Episode 5 Apple Making a Game Console? EA to be bought?</title>
<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Episode 5 Apple Making a Game Console? EA to be bought?</itunes:summary>
<description>In this delayed installment of the Emperor's Court, guest co-host Highlander[1G] joins us to discuss the swirling rumors of Apple entering into the console gaming industry, EA being bought by either Apple or Microsoft, and an Emperor's Rant on Guitar Hero and Courtney Love!</description>
<itunes:duration>01:33:25</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Emperor,Court</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
<pubDate>Jan 26, 2010 01:53 AM</pubDate>
<enclosure type='audio/mpeg' url='http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec092309.mp3' length='1'/>
<link>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec092309.mp3</link>
<guid>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec092309.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Emperor's Court - Episode 4 Special Live Show!</title>
<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Episode 4 Special Live Show!</itunes:summary>
<description>This is the special live edition Emperor's Court with in studio guest host Highlander[1G]! This special edition runs 2 hours instead of the normal 1, and covers topics such as:

Email backlash over Napoleon: Total War hype

In depth look at Batman: Arkham's Asylum
Debate over Disney's purchase of Marvel and what it means

Emperor rants about Twilight fans of Twicon

enjoy!</description>
<itunes:duration>02:03:13</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Emperor,Court</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
<pubDate>Jan 26, 2010 01:51 AM</pubDate>
<enclosure type='audio/mpeg' url='http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec090109.mp3' length='1'/>
<link>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec090109.mp3</link>
<guid>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec090109.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Emperor's Court - Episode 3  FFIV After Years, NTW, Console FPS'ers Suck, Video Games make you fat!</title>
<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Episode 3  FFIV After Years, NTW, Console FPS'ers Suck, Video Games make you fat!</itunes:summary>
<description>In this installment of the Emperor's Court, we take a first look at Creative Assembly's Napoleon: Total War, give a review of Square-Enix's WiiWare sequel to Final Fantasy 4, The After Years. We also read over some articles about scientific studies that say video games and the Internet make people fat and anti-social, a gaming camp for kids, and an Emperor Rant (tm) about PC FPS Gamers > Console FPS Gamers.</description>
<itunes:duration>01:16:14</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Emperor,Court</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
<pubDate>Jan 26, 2010 01:49 AM</pubDate>
<enclosure type='audio/mpeg' url='http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec082809.mp3' length='1'/>
<link>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec082809.mp3</link>
<guid>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec082809.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Emperor's Court - Episode 2 WoW Expo Cataclysm, SC2, Game Industry dying, Wii hackers and more!</title>
<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Episode 2 WoW Expo Cataclysm, SC2, Game Industry dying, Wii hackers and more!</itunes:summary>
<description>Well after a 1 day delay due to inclement weather and a host of technical nightmares, the show is here and to compensate for your longer wait time, the show is 93 mins long as opposed to its usual 60. 

We discuss the new WOW Cataclysm, Starcraft 2, the death of the gaming industry, the 13th anniversary of the founding of Clan Imperial Guard, and a meltdown and rant by me about Wii hackers. BAH!

Due to the bed music interfering with the voice audio, I have reedited and removed the bed music for this episode. I don't know what went haywire with it, but Ill try to include it in the next installment.</description>
<itunes:duration>01:33:30</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Emperor,Court</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
<pubDate>Jan 26, 2010 01:47 AM</pubDate>
<enclosure type='audio/mpeg' url='http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec081809.mp3' length='1'/>
<link>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec081809.mp3</link>
<guid>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec081809.mp3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Emperor's Court - Episode 1 Return of the Court</title>
<itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary>Episode 1 Return of the Court</itunes:summary>
<description>In this first episode after a 4 year hiatus, Emperor discusses topics such as the EA Booth Babes fiasco, World of Warcraft Mobile Armory, Starcraft 2 LAN controversy, and a review of the PS3 game Dynasty Warriors 6: Empires. Ranting and raving to resume as Emperor provides insight into the insanity that is the gaming world.</description>
<itunes:duration>00:57:57</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Emperor,Court</itunes:keywords>
<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
<pubDate>Jan 26, 2010 01:44 AM</pubDate>
<enclosure type='audio/mpeg' url='http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec081109.mp3' length='1'/>
<link>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec081109.mp3</link>
<guid>http://emperorscourt.s3.amazonaws.com/ec081109.mp3</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
